{
    "id": "ed00cfa8015b4ab380ed280707119690",
    "title": "Infinitive With Or Without To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t let him ………………………….",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was not permitted ……………………….. to him.",
            "description": "Permit is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "to talk",
                "to talking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw them ………………………… the road.",
            "description": "See can be followed by object + ing form or bare infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "cross",
                "to cross",
                "crossing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard them …………………………. in the other room.",
            "description": "Hear can be followed by object + ing form or bare infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "talk",
                "to talk",
                "talking"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They encouraged me ………………………… another attempt.",
            "description": "Encourage is followed by a to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "to make",
                "making"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was told …………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quit",
                "quitting",
                "to quit"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I requested him …………………………. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "help",
                "to help",
                "helping"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher advised the students ……………………….. harder.",
            "description": "Advise is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "to work",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The poor slaves were made ………………………… day and night.",
            "description": "When make is used in its passive form, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "to work",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The cruel master made them ………………………… harder and harder.",
            "description": "Make is followed by object + bare infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "to work"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I want you ……………………….. by evening.",
            "description": "Want is followed by object + to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "to return",
                "return",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}